

CONTACT

thunyapornG@gmail.com

(+66)86493 0846

Bangkok, Thailand

SKILL

- HTML/CSS/SCSS
- JavaScript
- VueJS
- PHP Codeigniter Framework
- MySql
- Wordpress
- Version control (Git /Github)

SOFT SKILL

- Communication
- Problem-solving
- Ability to do a Research
- Adaptability
- Critical Thinking
- Time Management & Responsibility

PORTFOLIO



THUNYAPORN SANCHOMPOO

Frontend Developer

I'm Frontend Developer with 6+ years experience building efficient elegant and user-friendly websites. Experienced in working with development and UI/UX designer teams to create and develop various projects. Has a creative mindset to continuously improve and enhance the quality of work. I looking for an opportunity to grow frontend development skills in an innovative environment.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

May 2020 - Present

Piesoft Co., Ltd., Thailand

- Develop website based on any designs to (Vue.js)
 HTML/SCSS/JS in the quickest time possible. Work with
 UX/UI and other developers team to ensure that the
 website is functional and visually appealing.
- Developing features to enhance the user experience. Striking a balance between functional and aesthetic design.
- Ensure that the website is optimized for various devices.

WEB DEVELOPER

Dec 2016 - May 2020

Thinker Co., Ltd., Thailand

- Develop website/Landing page based on any design using HTML/SCSS/JS and build a Content Management System (CMS) using PHP (Codeigniter Framework) and create database in mysql.
- Ensure that the website is optimized for various devices and support Google SEO / Google Analytics
- Set up SSL/TLS Certificate and an FTP server in cPanel Hosting to upload the website to the live server.

PROGRAMMER (TRAINEE)

Jan 2016 - May 2016

TOT (Public) Co Ltd., Thailand

- Redesign the organization's website to be mobile responsive
- Create a system flowchart and create a database
- Design and develop an internal web application using PHP (Laravel Framework) along with CSS, HTML, and JavaScript, based on the study of the previous system which was in the form of a Windows Application.

EDUCATION

RANGSIT UNIVERSITY

2012 - 2016

Bachelor of Science (Computer Science)